American Vaudeville Museum collection, 1850s-2007 (bulk 1910s-1940s)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series VI: Theatres, ca. 1894-2007, 1.5 linear feet
  - Subseries 1: Theatre Postcards, Photographs, and Ephemera, ca. 1894-2004
    - Illinois (Box 17, Folder 2)
      Vaudeville Theatre, formerly the Iroquois Theatre (Chicago, Ill.)
    - Maryland (Box 17, Folder 3)
      Maryland Theatre and Hotel Kernan (Baltimore, Md.) - 2 views
    - Massachusetts (Box 17, Folder 4)
      Adam's House and Keith's Theatre (Boston, Mass.) 1924 - 2 versions
      B.F. Keith's New Theatre (Boston, Mass.) - booklet, 44 p., ca. 1894
      Boston Music Hall (Boston, Mass.) - tickets from "All Star Vaudeville", 1905
      Colonial Theatre (Onset, Mass.)
      Cordon's Theatre (Chelsea, Mass.)
      Gaiety Theatre Building (Boston, Mass.)
      Happyland Vaudeville (Boston, Mass.) - admission ticket
      Keith's Theatre (Boston, Mass.) - King's Booklets, a souvenir of Keith's Boston Theatre, ca. 1900
      Keith's Vaudeville (Brockton, Mass.)
      RKO Keith's (Boston, Mass.)
      Tremont Theatre (Boston, Mass.) - 2 versions
    - Michigan (Box 17, Folder 5)
      Fisher Theatre (Detroit, Mich.) (booklet, 31 p.; Graven & Mayger, Architects; Theatre Historical Society of America annual, no. 31) 2004
      Orpheum Theatre (Detroit, Mich.)
      Temple Theatre (Detroit, Mich.) - 2 copies
    - Missouri (Box 17, Folder 6)
      New Orpheum Theatre (Kansas City, Mo.)
      Orpheum Theatre (Kansas City, Mo.)
    - Nebraska (Box 17, Folder 7)
      Burwood Theatre (Omaha, Neb.)
      Orpheum Theatre (Lincoln, Neb.)
      Orpheum Theatre (Omaha, Neb.)
      World Theatre (Omaha, Neb.)
    - New Jersey (Box 17, Folder 8)
      Boardwalk (Atlantic City, N.J.)
      Lyric Theatre (Summit, N.J.)
      Waldmann's Theatre (Newark, N.J.)
    - New York (Box 17, Folder 9)
      B.F. Keith's Palace Theatre (New York, N.Y.) - postcard of playbill, 1915
      B.F. Keith's Vaudeville Theatre (Syracuse, N.Y.)
      Bowery (New York, N.Y.)
      Club House of the National Vaudeville Artists (New York, N.Y.)
      Harry Hills Variety Theatre (New York, N.Y.)
      Hippodrome (New York, N.Y.) - 2 postcard views and photograph
      The Lambs (New York, N.Y.) - 73rd consecutive weekly function - Lambs & M. Corps - Oct. 13, 1943; page from guestbook
      Memorial Hall (Gloversville, N.Y.)
      On Stage: A Photographic Reminiscence of New York Theater, 1895-1915; a book of postcards. Museum of the City of New York, The Byron Collection. (San Francisco: Pomegranate Press, 1999)
      Places of Amusement - New York City, Nov. 1882 - miniature brochure
      RKO Palace Theatre (New York, N.Y.)
      Shea's Theatre (Buffalo, N.Y.)
      Shubert Theatre (Utica, N.Y.)
      Temple Theater (Rochester, N.Y.)
      Union Square (New York, N.Y.)
    - Ohio (Box 17, Folder 10)
      B.F. Keith Vaudeville (Cleveland, Ohio)
      Keith Vaudeville (Columbus, Ohio)
    - Pennsylvania (Box 17, Folder 11)
      Air Dome (Wilkinsburg, Penn.)
      Keith's Theatre (Philadelphia, Pa.) - postcard, and page from Philadelphia Guide
      Neumeyer Theatre (Easton, Pa.)
      Orpheum Theatre (Allentown, Pa.)
      Poli's Theatre (Wilkes Barre, Pa.)
      Star Theatre (Monessen, Pa.)
    - Rhode Island (Box 17, Folder 12)
      Ball Room, Vanity Fair (Providence, R.I.)
      Imperial Theatre (Providence, R.I.)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 13)
      Bijou Theatre (Melbourne, Australia)
      Bird Cage Theatre (Tombstone, Ariz.) - photograph
      Keith's New Theatre (Portland, Me.)
      Majestic Theatre (Fort Worth, Tex.)
      Palace, Sunderland (Hippodrome, Salford, England)
      Palace Theatre (Wis.)
      Unidentified theatre (Melbourne, Australia)
  - Subseries 2: Theatre Programs, 1892-2007
    This subseries is a collection of programs and playbills from theatres across the United States, including B.F. Keith's, Orpheum, and RKO theatres. There are also some theatre publicity materials and arts periodicals, and flyers from music publishing houses and from suppliers of playbills and posters for stage productions. They are organized alphabetically by theatre name.
    - The Alex Theatre (Glendale, Calif.) 2002 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - American Repertory Theatre (Cambridge, Mass.) 2004 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - B.F. Keith's (Columbus, Ohio) 1910-1911 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - B.F. Keith's New Theatre (Philadelphia, Pa.) 1911-1912, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - B.F. Keith's New Theatre (Providence, R.I.) 1899 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - B.F. Keith's Palace Theatre (New York, N.Y.) 1925 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - B.F. Keith's Theatre (Boston, Mass.) 1905, 1909-1910, 1917; souvenir booklet, undated; and playbills 1920-1925 (photocopies) (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - B.F. Keith's Theatre (Columbus, Ohio),"The Vaudeville Bill" 1917 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - B.F. Keith's Theatre (Portland, Me.) 1913 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - B.F. Keith's Theatre (Providence, R.I.) 1911 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Big Auditorium (Chicago, Ill.) ca. 1906 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Bijou Theatre (Bangor, Me.) 1922 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Boston Arts (Boston, Mass.) - magazine March 1970 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Boston Arts Festival (Boston, Mass.) - program of events 1955 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Boston Music Hall (Boston, Mass.) 1901 - cover photocopy; 1904-1905 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Castle Square Theatre (Boston, Mass.) 1898, 1903 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Chase Theatres (Washington, D.C.) 1903 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Clark Theatre (Chicago, Ill.) ca. 1916 or 1922 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Clunie Orpheum Theatre (Sacramento, Calif.) 1918 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Colonial Theatre (Boston, Mass.) 1910-1911, 1919-1921, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Columbia Music Hall (Boston, Mass.) 1907-1908 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Curran Theatre (San Francisco, Calif.) - "The Playgoer", 1943 - "Laugh Time" ( Frank Fay, Ethel Waters, Bert Wheeler) (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Duchess Theatre (London, England) 1954 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - E.F. Albee Theatre (Providence, R.I.) 1919, ca. 1925 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Federal Theatre / Copley Theatre (Boston, Mass.) - Works Progress Administration 1936 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Forty-fourth Street Theatre (New York, N.Y.) 1939 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Gayety Theatre (Boston, Mass.) 1929 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Geary Theatre (San Francisco, Calif.) - flyer for "The Doughgirls" by Joseph Fields, staged by George S. Kaufman ca. 1943 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Grand Opera (Minneapolis, Minn.) 1892 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Hammerstein's Victoria (New York, N.Y.) 1905 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Hathaway's (Boston, Mass.) 1906-1907 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Hollis St. Theatre (Boston, Mass.) 1910 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Koster & Bial's Music Hall (New York, N.Y.) ca. 1900 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Lakewood Theatre (Skowhegan, Me.) 1932 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Light Opera of New York (New York, N.Y.) - photocopy 2007 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Manhattan Theatre Colony (Ogunquit, Me.) 1934 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Maryland Theatre (Baltimore, Md.) 1919-1920 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - National Theatre (Dayton, Ohio) 1908 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - New Palace - RKO Vaudeville (New York, N.Y.) 1929 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - New Victory Theater (New York, N.Y.) March/April 2004 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Nixon & Zimmerman's Academy of Music (Baltimore, Md.) 1899-1900 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - NY City Center, Encores! (New York, N.Y.) 2007 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Ocean Road School (Point Pleasant, N.J.) 1959 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Olympia (San Francisco, Calif.) 1901 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Open Theatre, Loeb Drama Center, Harvard (Cambridge, Mass.) 1968 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Orpheum Theatre (Los Angeles, Calif.) 1929 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Orpheum Theatre (South Bend, Ind.) 1911 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Osbornville School (Brick Township, N.J.) 1957, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Palace Theatre (New York, N.Y.) - "Sarah Bernhardt in Vaudeville" 1912 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Philharmonic Auditorium (Los Angeles, Calif.) 1924 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Phoenix Theatre (London, England) 1953 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Poli's Theatre (Hartford, Conn.) 1907 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Proctor's Palace Theatre (Yonkers, N.Y.) - photocopy 1920 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - The Repertory Dance Theatre (Salt Lake City, Utah) 1970 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - RKO Albee (Cincinnati, Ohio) 1949-1950 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - RKO Palace (Rochester, N.Y.) 1949 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Royce Hall, UCLA (Los Angeles, Calif.) - Les Ballets Trockadero de Monte Carlo 1976 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Sam S. Shubert Theatre/Chestnut Street Opera House (New York, N.Y.) 1923 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Sampliner - advertisements, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Sargent School (North Andover, Mass.?) 1910 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Selwyn's Park Square Theatre (Boston, Mass.) 1919 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - St. James Theatre (London, England) 1954 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Strand Theatre (Boston, Mass.) - "Floor Lore, A History of Hip-Hop", The Floor Lords 2002 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Symphony Space (New York, N.Y.) 2007 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Theater Offensive (Boston, Mass.) - "Unitard" 2002, 1920 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Tremont Theatre (Boston, Mass.) 1905, 1920 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Vaudeville Theatre (London, England) ca. 1935 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - White Barn Theatre (Westport, Conn.) - "Thirty Years of the White Barn Theatre" 1978 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Wilbur Theatre (Boston, Mass.) 1976 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Winter Garden Theatre (New York, N.Y.) 1934, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Wyndham's Theatre (London, England) 1954 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Theatre programs - color reproductions (Box 19, Folder 24)
      B.F. Keith's Palace Theatre (New York, N.Y.)
      The Circle (New York, N.Y.)
      Daly's Theatre (New York, N.Y.)
      Earle Theatre (Philadelphia, Pa.)
      Gaiety Theatre (New York, N.Y.)
      Lew Fields Herald Square Theatre (New York, N.Y.)
      New Amsterdam Theatre (New York, N.Y.)
      Orpheum Circuit
      Pantages Theatre (Sacramento, Calif.)
      White House lawn, Jenny Lind concert (President and Mrs. M. Fillmore)
  - Subseries 3: Souvenir Programs, 1899-ca. 2003
    This subseries comprises souvenir programs from revues, Broadway shows, musicals, and plays. They are organized alphabetically by production title, or in some cases by another cover title when there is no evident production title. The earliest is an 1899 program from Koster & Bial's Music Hall in New York. There are two Hippodrome souvenir programs (1918 and 1924) and a Ziegfeld Follies program (1942-43). Productions include "Showtime" with George Jessel (1943) and "Tobacco Road" with James Barton (1936).
    - "As the Girls Go" ( Bobby Clark, Irene Rich) 1948 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - B.F. Keith's New York Hippodrome, "Novelties from All Parts of the Earth" - Bill of International Artists Aug. 1924, Oct. 1924, Feb. 1925 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - "Big Time" ( Ed Wynn) 1921 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - "The Biggest Show of '51" ( Duke Ellington, Nat "King" Cole, Sarah Vaughan, etc.) 1951 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - "Bless You All" ( Jules Munshin, Mary McCarty, Pearl Bailey, etc.) 1950 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - "Curtain Time" ( Chico Marx, Connee Boswell, etc.) 1945 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - George Jessel's "High Kickers" with Sophie Tucker, Chaz Chase, York and King. 1941 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Hippodrome Souvenir Book, Charles Dillingham presents "Everything", a Mammoth Musical Spectacle 1918 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - "Hold Your Horses" ( Joe Cook) 1933 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - "Holiday on Ice of 1955", "Holiday on Ice of 1961" (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Horace Heidt, "Stars on Parade" 1950 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - James Barton in "Tobacco Road" 1936 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - John Murray Anderson's "Almanac" ( Hermione Gingold, Billy De Wolfe, Harry Belafonte, Orson Bean) 1953-54 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - "Jumbo" ( Billy Rose production at the Hippodrome) 1935 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Koster & Bial's Music Hall (New York) ( Sadie Probst, The Meeker-Baker Trio, Zelma Rawlston, etc.) 1899 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - "Let's Face It!" ( Danny Kaye; Cole Porter songs) 1941 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Lew Brown's Musical Comedy "Yokel Boy" ( Buddy Ebsen, Judy Canova, and Phil Silvers, etc.) 1940 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - " Maurice Chevalier at 77" (Nine O'Clock Theatre series) 1965 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - "Mrs. Steinberg and Byker Boy" 1999 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - "The New B.F. Keith Memorial Theatre" (Boston, Mass.) 1928, (and letter to the editor by Frank Cullen, Boston Sunday Herald, Feb. 26, 1995) (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - "Oklahoma!" (Los Angeles Civic Light Opera) 1959 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - "Priorities of 1942" ( Lou Holtz, Willie Howard, Hazel Scott, Ben Bernie, Paul Draper, etc.) 1942 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - "Show Time" ( George Jessel, Jack Haley, Ella Logan, The De Marcos, etc.) 1943 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - "Sugar Babies", The Burlesque Musical ( Mickey Rooney, Ann Miller; Mickey Deems) ) 1979 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Todd Robbins' "Carnival Knowledge", Soho Playhouse ca. 2003 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Victor Herbert's "The Red Mill" ( Eddie Foy Jr., Jack Whiting, etc.) 1945 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - "West Side Story", A New Musical (directed by Jerome Robbins) 1957 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - "Ziegfeld Follies" ( Milton Berle, Ilona Massey, Arthur Treacher) 1942-43 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Subseries 4: Boston Theatre Programs, ca.1920-1952
    The items in this subseries were donated to the American Vaudeville Museum collection by G. M. Sanborn of the Massachusetts State Transportation Library.
    These programs are organized alphabetically by theatre, with featured programs indicated. Multiple programs for a given theatre are listed chronologically. They include the "Ziegfeld Follies" (1922) at the New Amsterdam Theatre and "Candida" (1925) at the Plymouth Theatre. A few are from New York rather than Boston theatres; those are indicated as such. Some theatre-related publications other than programs are also located here.
    - Boston Opera House (Box 21, Folder 1)
      "The Miracle" 1925
    - The Capitol, A Publix Theatre (Box 21, Folder 2)
      "The Wolf of Wall Street" 1929
    - Colonial Theatre (Box 21, Folder 3)
      "Stepping Stones" 1925
      "Three Cheers" 1929
    - Community Service of Boston Inc. (Box 21, Folder 4)
      "Community Songs" (not a theatre program) undated (after 1920)
    - Copley Theatre (Box 21, Folder 5)
      "The Bellamy Trial" 1928
      "The Wrecker" 1928
      "The Ringer" 1929
      "The Whispering Gallery" 1929
    - Cort Theatre (New York) (Box 21, Folder 6)
      "Only 38" 1921
    - Dollhouse Theatre (Box 21, Folder 7)
      "Medea" 1999
    - Film Guild Cinema (New York) (Box 21, Folder 8)
      "The House of Shadow Silence" 1929
      "Waterloo" 1929
    - George M. Cohan Theatre (New York) (Box 21, Folder 9)
      "Across the World with Mr. & Mrs. Martin Johnson" 1930
    - Greenwich Village Theatre (New York) (Box 21, Folder 10)
      "The Beggar's Opera" 1920
    - Hollis Street Theatre (Box 21, Folder 11)
      "Peter Pan" (Civic Repertory Theatre, New York, tour) 1926
      "Marco Millions" 1928
      "Porgy" 1928
    - Majestic Theatre (Box 21, Folder 12)
      "Cavalcade" 1933
      "White Lilacs" 1929
    - Metropolitan (Box 21, Folder 13)
      "Three Sinners" 1928
    - New Amsterdam Theatre (Box 21, Folder 14)
      "Ziegfeld Follies" 1922
    - New York Amusements (New York) week of Apr. 8, 1929 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      "The Love Duel" - Ethel Barrymore, at the Barrymore Theatre (on cover)
    - New Park Theatre (Box 21, Folder 16)
      "The Dark" ca. 1927
    - Plymouth Theatre (Box 21, Folder 17)
      "Candida" 1925
      "Applesauce" 1926
      "The Play's the Thing" 1928
      "The Command to Love" 1929
      "Emlyn Williams as Charles Dickens" ca. 1952
    - Publix Theatres (Box 21, Folder 18)
      "The Vagabond King" (promotional booklet for motion picture) 1930
    - Repertory Theatre of Boston (Box 21, Folder 19)
      "Heartbreak House" 1926
      "R.U.R." (Rossum's Universal Robots) 1926
    - Shubert-Plymouth Theatre (Box 21, Folder 20)
      "The Command to Love" ca. 1929
    - Shubert Theatre (Box 21, Folder 21)
      "George White's Scandals" ca. 1928
      "Greenwich Village Follies" ca. 1921-26
      "Dark of the Moon" 1945
      "Gentlemen Prefer Blondes" ( Carol Channing) 1952
      "Paris '90" ( Cornelia Otis Skinner) 1952
    - Shubert-Majestic Theatre (Box 21, Folder 22)
      "Good News" ca. 1925
      "A Connecticut Yankee" ca. 1927
    - Shubert-Wilbur Theatre (Box 21, Folder 23)
      "The Road to Rome" 1927
      "The Trial of May Dugan" 1929
    - Tributary Theatre of Boston (Box 21, Folder 24)
      Flyer ca. 1945
    - Wilbur Theatre (Box 21, Folder 25)
      "The Royal Family" 1929
      "Dunnigan's Daughter" 1945
- Series VII: Photographs, 1906-1961, bulk ca. 1910s-1940s, 1 linear foot
  This series consists of miscellaneous photographs, mostly 11 x 14 inches; some are offset reproductions rather than actual photographic prints. Many more photographs can be found in the Performers files and the individual collections.
  There are two general categories. The first group consists primarily of publicity portraits of entertainers. The photographs are listed here in alphabetical order by subject's surname. The second group consists of movie stills, mostly 11 x 14 inches. Many of them are from an unidentified 1940 movie, with image numbers SMC-.
  - Photographs: Portraits, identified (Box 22, Folder 1)
    Jeanette Alabassi, by Strand (N.Y.)
    Phil Baker in "Pleasure Bound", Majestic Theatre, by George Maillard Kesslere (N.Y.)
    Ray Bolger, by Vandamm Studio (N.Y.)
    Ray Bolger [in "Sunny"] - 2 photos
    Walter Clinton, by Mitchell (N.Y.)
    Joe Frisco, by Mitchell (N.Y.)
    Joe E. Lewis, by Bloom (Chicago)
    Flourney Miller - formerly of Miller & Lyles, "Blackbirds of 1930", by Mitchell (N.Y.)
    Mae Murray, by Bloom (Chicago)
    Valerie Parks, by Bruno (Hollywood)
    Julia Rooney, by Mitchell (N.Y.)
    Rosita Royce, by Bruno (Hollywood)
  - Photographs: Ruth St. Denis, (photomechanical process) (Box 22, Folder 2)
    Ruth St. Denis as "Radha", 1906, by Marcus Blechman
    Ruth St. Denis in "Black Nautch", 1927, by Marcus Blechman
    [Ruth St. Denis in] "White Jade", 1927, by Marcus Blechman
    Ruth St. Denis in "Tagore Poem", 1929, by Marcus Blechman
    The Spirit of Ruth St. Denis, 1950, by Phil Baribault
    Photo of Ruth St. Denis in foyer of the Museum of the City of New York, 1961, by Marcus Blechman
  - Photographs: Miscellaneous (Box 22, Folder 3)
    "Going to Town" [burlesque revue], by Canell (N.Y.)
    [unidentified woman holding black gauze fabric]
    [unidentified woman draped in swirling-pattern gauze fabric]
    [unidentified couple in straw and bowler hats, stage role], by Cadia? (N.Y.)
    [unidentified female portrait, bleached]
    [Yiddish theater façade and street scene]
  - Movie stills: "The Flame of New Orleans", 1941 (Marlene Dietrich and Mischa Auer) - 2 photos (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Movie stills: "Sunny" (Anna Neagle and John Carroll) - 5 photos (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Movie stills: "Mr. and Mrs. Smith" (Gene Raymond, Robert Montgomery, Carole Lombard) - 2 photos (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Movie stills: Unidentified film - 18 photos (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Movie stills: Miscellaneous (Box 22, Folder 8)
    Merle Oberon
    Emily Smith, as Peas, in Shine On Harvest Moon. A Warner Bros. First National Picture
    [still from "The Maltese Falcon" - Humphrey Bogart, Mary Astor, Peter Lorre, Sydney Greenstreet]
    [still from silent? film - couple holding hands by window, locomotive approaching]
- Series VIII: Posters and Oversize Items, ca. 1850s-1980s, 4 linear feet
  This series comprises vintage and reproduced posters and display boards. In addition, there is a cut-out toy figure, a group of photos matted together, a portfolio cover, and a newspaper article, housed here for reasons of size. Four oversize photographs from the Dixon-Freeman collection are also stored here. Larger posters are housed separately in oversize storage.
  - (Box 23)
    - "Argentine Nights, starring The Ritz Brothers and The Andrews Sisters", 1940 poster, Realart Pictures
    - " Basil Rathbone, Boris Karloff, Bela Lugosi in Son of Frankenstein", 1939 poster (reproduction)
    - "Bloolips in London's Finest Comedy, Teenage Trash", 1987
    - " Carl Laemmle presents Dracula, the vampire thriller", 1931 poster (reproduction)
    - Dixon-Freeman collection - photographs
      [ Jessica Dixon], by Witzel (L.A.)
      [ Frank Freeman]
      [ Jessica Dixon in Mexican costume]
      [ Jessica Dixon with Mexican ensemble], by Stagg
    - Duncan Sisters, 2 photographs and newspaper image, 1920s-1950s, matted together
    - "F.B.O. presents Fred Thompson and his remarkable horse Silver King in 'Thundering Hoofs'", 1924 poster, Film Booking Offices (color photocopy)
    - " Fanny Brice as Baby Snooks", cut-out figure, 1950, 16 in., with Tums ad and instructions on verso
    - "The Four Step Brothers, America's foremost dancing quartet ", Marcus Glaser, Charles Hogan Agency, Chicago
    - "Harry Qubey's Dog Circus" (reproduction)
    - "Hellzapoppin'" starring Olsen and Johnson with Martha Raye, 1941 (modern reproduction), (from the Olsen and Johnson collection)
    - "The Jewess! Or, The Council of Constance." ca. 1850s, Boston Museum playbill, approx. 19 x 9 in.
    - Minstrel show sign - no text
    - "The New Ravel, Humpty-Dumpty", ca. 1900, cardboard poster
    - " Orson Welles, Citizen Kane", 1941 poster (reproduction)
    - " Paul Wenzel, producing original, clown-walk-arounds", Charles Hogan Agency, Chicago
    - Standard Theatre program (New York, week ending Apr 20, 1889)
    - "Twelve new Gibson Girls, hitherto unpublished", red portfolio cover, lacking original print contents, (received with Dixon-Freeman collection)
    - "The 'Two Black Crows': pitiful end of one of the Moran and Mack team of popular merrymakers recalls some of the jokes and funny dialogues which amused Americans for many years." ( American Weekly article, 1937)
    - "Vaudeville's High-Water Mark - All-Star Bill Houdini Frank McIntyre Joe Cook ", 1922 playbill
    - "Willie, West & McGinty", 1940s, George A. Hamid and Son
  - Mae West, 1931, Paramount poster mounted on particle board, 26.5 x 20 in. (Box 24)
  - Color lithograph posters, 1907-08, approx. 40 x 80 in. each (Box Oversize Storage)
    Clown heads (2 posters)
    Dancing girls (3 posters)
    Somersaulting bicycle act (1 poster)
  - Posters (Box Oversize Storage)
    "George Primrose and His Minstrels / Olsen & Johnson / ", Crystal playbill, 42 x 14 in.
    "'Skipper' Don Mills / The Four Gondoliers / Blib and Blob / ", 1934 playbill, 3 ft. 6 in. x 2 ft. 4 in.
    (received as part of the Gondoliers/Ricci collection)
    "Pat Rooney, Jr. / George & Dixie, Radio Stars / other big acts - screen: Sailors On Leave", ca. 1941 playbill
    "Salem Paramount / Salem Empire, New Year's Eve Mammoth", ca. 1940 playbill
    "Vaudeville Revue featuring Follies stars Buster West & Co.", ca. 1940 playbill
    "Fort Massacre, starring Joel McCrea", 1958 movie poster
- Series IX: Sheet Music, 1859-1945 (bulk 1905-1935), 2 linear feet
  This series encompasses popular sheet music from the late 1890s to the mid-1940s, as well as two opera librettos from 1859 and the 1920s. Most are the original item; a few are color photocopies. They are arranged alphabetically by title. Several are associated with shows such as the Ziegfeld Follies. Each features images of one or more performers on the cover.